Previously on Friends:
Erica, are you okay?
Yeah, you know, maybe I ate too much.
I keep getting these stomachaches. They come and go, like, every few minutes.
Oh, my God.
Relax, we'll just get her some antacids.
She doesn't have a stomachache! She's in labor!
Qh, my God!
If you think that I didn't say goodbye...
...because you don't mean as much to me as everybody else, you're wrong.
It's because you mean more to me.
Rash!
What?
Hey.
Ha, ha.
Shh. Go back to sleep. I have to go home.
Oh, God. This was amazing.
It really was.
You've learned some new moves.
Yeah, well, uh, this guy at work gave me Sex for Dummies as a joke.
Ah.
Who's laughing now?
I am.
Breathe. Breathe. Breathe.
Okay. Good.
Next time, can I say "breathe"?
No. Last time, you said it like Dracula, and it scared her.
Can I get you anything? Want more ice chips?
No, I'm okay.
All right. I'll be right back.
Where you going?
To use the bathroom.
You can't leave me alone with her.
What?
This is exactly the kind of social situation...
...that I am not comfortable with.
What kind of social situation are you comfortable with?
It's just that we've never spent any time, you know, alone together.
You'll be fine. You won't, but I'll be back in two minutes.
Okay.
So, uh, any plans for the summer?
I don't know. Maybe church camp.
Ha...
May not want to mention this.
So you ever wonder which is worse?
You know, going through labor or getting kicked in the nuts?
What?
Oh, it's just interesting.
You know, because no one will ever know because no one can experience both.
One of life's great unanswerable questions.
I mean, who knows?
Maybe there's something even more painful than those things.
Like this.
Come in.
Morning.
Hey.
What's that?
Oh, it's my housewarming present for Monica and Chandler.
That's a baby chick and duck.
Uh-huh.
And I named them Chick Jr. and Duck Jr.
I did not see that coming.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
They'll love it at that new house. It has that big backyard.
And when they're old, they can go to that farm...
...that Chandler took the other chick and duck to.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's a shame people can't visit there.
That is the rule though.
Guess what. You're almost an uncle.
What?
Erica went into labor. Monica and Chandler are at the hospital right now.
Oh, my God!
I have a feeling it's gonna be a girl.
Phoebe, you were sure Ben was gonna be a girl.
Have you seen him throw a ball'?
Is Rachel here?
Uh, I think she's still asleep.
Hey, hey, hey. How did it go with you guys last night?
She seemed pretty pissed at you.
We, uh... You know, we worked things out.
What's that smile? Did something happen with you two?
Hey, I'm not one to kiss and tell.
Uh, but I'm also not one to have sex and shut up. We totally did it.
Oh, my God. You and Rachel?
I know, it's pretty great.
So, what does that mean?
Are you guys getting back together?
Oh, I don't know.
We didn't really get to talk.
But do you want to get back together?
I don't know.
It was incredible. I mean, it just felt so right.
When I was holding her, I mean, I never wanted to let her go.
Know what? Yeah, I do. I want to be together.
Yay!
Shh!
So is she still going to Paris?
Wow, I hadn't thought of that. I hope not.
This is, like, the best day ever. Ever. You guys might get back together.
Monica and Chandler get their baby. There are chicks and ducks...
...in the world again.
Oh. I feel like I'm in a musical.
When the sun comes up Bright and beamin'
And the moon comes
Morning.
Guess you'll never know how it ends.
Hey.
Hi.
Hi. How'd you sleep?
Good. You?
Good.
I'll bet you did.
Uh, would you guys mind giving us a minute?
Sure. Yeah. Just keep an eye on the chick and duck.
Chick and the duck'? Didn't they die...?
Dive. Yeah, they dove. Headfirst into fun on the farm.
So...
Morning.
You too.
Last night was just wonderful.
Oh, it really was.
I woke up today with the biggest smile on my face.
I know, me too. It was...
You know, it was like one of those things you think is never gonna happen.
And then it does, and it's everything you want it to be.
I know. It was just...
It's just the perfect way to say goodbye.
Just a little bit more, honey.
Oh, man, this hurts!
Is it really that bad?
Uh-huh.
I think it's time to kick you in the nuts and see which is worse.
The baby's head is crowning.
Oh, my God! That is the most beautiful top of a head I have ever seen.
Chandler, you have to see this.
I'm okay.
You don't want to miss this. This is the birth of your child.
It's the miracle of life.
All right.
Wow, that is one disgusting miracle.
Start pushing. Here we go.
Here come the shoulders.
It's a boy.
Is he okay?
He's just fine.
You did it.
It's a baby.
A beautiful little baby. And some other stuff I'm gonna pretend I don't see.
Would you like to cut the umbilical cord?
Okay.
Well, that's spongy.
Oh...
Hey, handsome.
I'll love you so much that no woman is ever gonna be good enough for you.
We are so lucky.
I know.
He has your eyes.
I mean, I know that's not possible, but he does.
We'll just get him cleaned up a bit.
Okay.
Oh, my God, he's beautiful.
Thank you so much.
I'm really happy for you guys.
How do you feel?
I'm tired.
You don't have that much time to relax. The other one will be along in a minute.
I'm sorry, who should be along in a what, now?
The next baby should be along in a minute.
We only ordered one.
You know it's twins, right?
Oh, yeah.
These are the faces of two people in the know.
I can't believe you didn't know its twins. This has never happened before.
Well, gosh. That makes me feel so special and good.
Did you know it was twins?
Yeah, it's here in the paperwork we got from the clinic.
Did anybody tell you?
I don't think so.
Although, they did mention something about two heartbeats...
...but I thought that was just mine and the baby's.
They said, "Both heartbeats are strong."
And I thought, "Well, that's good, because I'm having a baby."
This is unbelievable.
Twins actually run in my family.
Interesting.
Can I see you for a second?
What do we do?
What do you mean, "What do we do?"
Twins!
Chandler, you're panicking.
Uh-huh! Join me, won't you?
What do you say we keep one and then just have an option on the other one?
We can't split them up.
Why not?
We could give each of them half a medallion.
And then years later, they'll find each other...
...and be reunited. I mean, that's a great day for everybody.
Okay. What if the person who adopts the other one is horrible?
What if they're not? What if it's adopted by a king?
Yeah. Because I hear the king is looking to adopt.
Monica, we are not ready to have two babies.
That doesn't matter. We have waited so long for this.
I don't care if it's two babies. I don't care if it's three babies.
I don't care if the entire cast of Eight Is Enough comes out of there.
We are taking them home because they are our children.
Okay. Shh.
Qkay
Qkay!
Okay.
It looks like we're about ready over here. Come on, Erica.
Start pushing again now.
Here she comes.
She? It's a girl?
Yeah.
Well, now we have one of each.
And that's enough.
And then she said it was the perfect way to say goodbye.
Oh, my God.
What did you say?
Nothing. What do you say to that?
Ross, you've got to tell her how you feel.
No way.
Well, you can't just give up.
Is that what a dinosaur would do?
What?
I'm just trying to speak your language.
Ross, Rachel doesn't know that you even wanna get back together.
If she did, she might feel differently. She might not even go.
You really think so?
I'm telling you!
Oh, okay, this is the part of the musical where there'd be a good, convincing song.
Don't take no for an answer
Don't let love fly away
Hi.
Can't a girl finish a song around here?
Hey.
Hi. So I dropped Emma off at my mom's.
Okay.
You're not taking her tonight?
No, we decided that I'd go ahead and set up first...
...then my mom would bring Emma to Paris on Sunday.
Wow. Eight-hour flight with a baby. Good luck, Mom.
Are you kidding? Eight hours with my mom talking about Atkins. Good luck, Emma.
All right. You know what? You're right. I should at least tell her how I feel.
Ross. Wait, wait.
What? What?
Could you get me a muffin?
Rachel?
Yeah?
I know you're leaving tonight, but I just have to tell you.
I love you.
Now, I don't know if that changes your plans at all.
But I thought you should know.
Gunther.
I love you too. Probably not in the same way.
But I do. And when I'm in a café having coffee...
...or I see a man with hair brighter than the sun...
...I'll think of you.
Bye, you guys.
Bye.
Qh, my God!
Unbelievable.
Hey, you know what might help?
I'm not getting you a muffin!
Do you think they recognize each other from in there?
Maybe. Unless they're like people who've lived in apartments...
...next to each other for years, then one day they're pushed through a vagina...
...and they meet.
We're going to take Erica to Recovery now.
There's something that we wanted to tell you.
We decided to name the girl baby Erica.
Oh, my God, that's just like my name!
Son of a gun, it is.
Anyway, I'm gonna go get some rest.
I'm really glad I picked you guys. You're gonna make great parents.
Even Chandler.
Okay, well, bye.
Bye.
We'll call you.
Okay.
Have fun at church camp.
Look at these little bunnies.
I know.
You ready to trade?
Qkay
Qkay-
Okay. Let's see.
We could trade later.
Yeah, I'm good.
Hey, what are you working on?
A "welcome home" sign for the baby.
How sweet! Oh, is that the baby?
No, I sat in the paint.
Hey.
So did you talk to Rachel?
No. And I'm not going to.
What?
Why not?
She's just gonna shoot me down.
You saw what happened with Gunther. That did not look like fun.
How can you compare yourself to Gunther?
I mean, sure, he's sexy in a more obvious way.
You have a relationship with her. You slept together last night.
Yeah, and she still wants to go. It's pretty clear where she is.
Yeah, I know what you mean. I mean, sometimes...
Uh, Joe.
Damn it!
If I were gonna tell her, I don't have to do it now.
Okay? I'll be seeing her again. We've got time.
No, you don't. She's going to Paris! She is going to meet somebody.
Do you know how many hot guys there are in Paris? It's a city of Gunthers.
Hey.
What do you have there?
Oh, I made a little something.
If I had more time to work on it, it'd be better, but...
Oh, my God, you did that yourself?
Honey, that's gorgeous.
You know, the baby can't read, Mike.
Hi. The car service just got here. I can't believe they're not home yet!
I have to catch my stupid plane. I want to see the baby.
Monica just called from the cab. She said they should be here any minute.
Apparently, there's some big surprise.
Yeah, did she sound happy about it?
Because my friend Ethel's baby was born with a teeny-tiny beard.
Welcome home.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my gosh.
Hey.
Hey, so, what is the big surprise?
Oh, my God!
How did this...?
Okay, awkward question. The hospital knows you took two, right?
Yes. It's twins.
Oh, my... They are so cute.
Now, what kinds are they?
This is a boy. And that's a girl.
Her name is Erica.
Hey, that pregnant girl's name was Erica.
Yeah. It's a shame you two didn't get to spend more time together.
Yeah, and we named the boy Jack, after Dad.
He's gonna be so happy.
Jack Bing. I love that.
It sounds like a '40s newspaper guy. You know, "Jack Bing, Morning Gazette.
I'm gonna blow this story wide open."
Oh, my gosh.
So beautiful.
I want one.
Oh, yeah? Well, tell me which one. I'll try to slip it in my coat.
Seriously. I mean, you want to make one of those?
One? How about a whole bunch?
Really?
Yeah. We can teach them to sing, and we could be like the von Trapp family.
Only without the Nazis. Although that sounds kind of dull.
I can't believe this. If I don't leave now, I'm gonna miss my plane.
I'm so glad you got to see the babies.
Me too.
I'm just sorry I'm not gonna be around to watch you two attempt to handle this.
All right. Oh, I can't say goodbye to you guys again.
I love you all so much.
Love you.
We love you.
Call us when you get there.
I will. Ross, come here.
I just want you to know...
...last night...
...I'll never forget it.
Neither will I.
All right. Now I really have to go.
Okay, au revoir.
Ugh.
They're gonna really hate me over there.
So you just let her go?
Yeah.
Hey, maybe that's for the best.
Yeah?
Yeah. You know, you just... Look, you gotta...
You gotta think about last night the way she does.
Okay? You know, maybe...
Maybe sleeping together was the perfect way to say goodbye.
But now she'll never know how he feels.
Maybe that's okay, you know?
Maybe it is better this way.
I mean, now... Now you can move on.
I mean, you've been trying to for so long.
Maybe now that you're on different continents...
Right?
Yeah.
Maybe now you can actually do it, you know.
You can finally get over her.
Yeah, that's true.
Except.
I don't want to get over her.
What?
I don't. I want to be with her.
Really?
Yeah. I'm going to go after her.
Yeah, you are!
Wait! Wait! Get your coat! Get your coat!
My coat.
This is so cool!
I have no idea what's going on, but I am excited!
What do you think she's gonna say?
I don't know.
But even if she shoots me down, at least I won't spend my life wondering...
...what would have happened. Where is my coat?
You didn't bring one! My cab's downstairs. I'll drive you to the airport.
Wish me luck.
Hurry!
Good luck!
There's no seat belts!
That's okay. If we hit anything...
...the engine will explode, so it's better if you're thrown from the car.
All right, all right. Let's do this.
Okay!
Hey!
80th and East End.
No. I don't take passengers.
The law makes you accept any fare.
You don't understand. This cab isn't real.
What's your medallion number?
My medallion number is, get out of the cab!
What?
Get out of the cab!
Oh, hey, can I give you guys your housewarming gift now?
Now, that you can do.
All right.
Chick Jr.? Duck Jr.?
Don't hide from Mama!
You can open your eyes now.
Are we off the bridge?
Yes!
Is the old woman on the bicycle still alive?
Yeah, she jumped right back up.
Oh, my God. Phoebe, slow down!
Do you want to get to Rachel in time?
Yes, but I don't want to die in your cab.
You should have thought of that before you got in!
Tollbooth.
What?
Toll booth !
Four bucks. There are quarters in the glove compartment.
Hurry!
Okay. Aah!
Damn, that window's clean.
Quack, quack. Tweet, tweet. Quack, quack.
Tweet, tweet. Quack, quack.
Tweet, tweet. Quack, quack. Tweet, tweet. Quack, tweet, quack.
We were wondering what was taking so long...
...but now we understand. You were doing this.
Okay. I wanted to surprise you, but...
For your housewarming gift, I got you a baby chick and a baby duck.
Really? You got us a chick and a duck?
Oh, great. Just what you want for a new house with infants. Bird feces!
But they must've jumped off the table. Now they're gone!
Don't worry, we'll find them.
I'm gonna go check on the twins.
All right.
Oh, God! What did I just step on?
It's okay. It's just an egg roll.
Oh.
You stepped on my egg roll?
I'm sorry. I didn't know to look for Chinese food on the floor.
Just put it on a plate and leave.
Okay. Let's find these birds.
All right.
Wait, wait. You hear that?
They're in the table!
Well, that can't be good.
We gotta get them out of there!
How?
Maybe we can lure them out. You know any birdcalls?
Oh, tons. I'm quite the Woodsman.
Well, maybe we can just tip the table a little.
Joey, wait! The ball!
So, what do we do?
Maybe we can open this up somehow.
Okay.
No. It's all glued together.
Does that mean we have to bust it open?
I don't know. Maybe.
Oh, my God.
I know. it's... It's the foosball table.
All right, you know what? We don't have a choice.
It's like I would have said in that sci-fi movie if I'd have gotten the part.
Those are our men in there, and we have to get them out...
...even if I have to sacrifice the most important thing in my life...
...my time machine.
Did that movie ever get made?
It did not.
Jack Weinberg, white courtesy phone. Jack Weinberg.
Ross, where are you going?
Uh, to talk to Rachel.
Isn't that why we took a ride in the death cab?
You're walking up to her at the gate?
Have you never chased anyone through the airport before?
Not since my cop show got canceled.
You have to get a ticket to get past security.
What? We're never gonna make it.
Not with that attitude. Now, haul ass!
Okay, if you could all walk slower, that'd be great.
Madame, your passport, please.
Oh, my God.
I was afraid I wouldn't remember any of my high school French.
But I understood every word you just said.
Your boarding pass, please.
Oh, sure.
Oh...
Shoot, I had it. Oh, I can't believe this.
Madame, if you don't have your...
I have it, I have it!
Oh...
Okay, I can't find it, but I remember that I was in seat 32C...
...because that's my bra size.
You must have your boarding pass...
You know what? If I was in 36D, we would not be having this problem.
Hi. I need a ticket.
Just one?
I drive you here, and I don't get to see how it works out?
Fine. Two tickets. I need two tickets.
We're on our honeymoon.
And the destination?
I don't care. Whatever's the cheapest.
I'm so lucky I married you.
Oh, shoot. Damn it. Where is it?
I found it. I found it. I told you I would find it.
In your face. You're a different person.
Sorry.
Okay. Flight 421, Paris.
I don't see it. Do you see it?
No. Did we miss it?
No, no, it's impossible. It doesn't leave for another 20 minutes.
Maybe we have the flight number wrong.
God.
Hello.
Hey, it's me. Here's Ross.
What?
Hey. Hey, listen...
You wouldn't believe the cute noises the twins are making. Wait, listen.
But Monica...
Monica. Monica. Monica. Monica.
I'm sorry. They were doing it before.
That's all right. Listen, listen.
Oh, wait, wait. Here they go again.
Monica. Monica. Monica. Monica.
Monica?
Isn't that cute?
That is precious! Listen...
I need Rachel's flight information.
Oh, okay.
All right, it's flight 421. Leaves at 8:40.
I have that. It's not on the board.
That's what it says here. Flight 421. Leaves at 8:40. Newark Airport.
What?
Newark Airport.
Why? Where are you?
JFK.
Don't worry, you guys! We're gonna get you out of there!
And we're also gonna buy you tiny bird hearing aids.
Okay. Here goes.
What's the matter?
I need to say goodbye to the table first.
I understand.
Okay.
Table...
...you have given us so many great times.
And you guys, Jordan, Victor, Joel...
All of you guys. What can I say?
You guys make us look good.
You want to say anything?
I don't know.
Except that, for one last time...
Good game. Good game. Good game.
Good game.
Yeah.
Okay. Here we go.
I can't do it.
Well, I can't do it either.
Hey. Did you find them?
Yeah. They're stuck inside the table.
And we have to bust it open, but neither of us can do it.
Oh, well, sure. It's got to be so hard.
I'll do it. Give me.
Phoebe! No, no, no!
Wow, I've never gone this fast before.
Phoebe, forget it, okay? Newark is, like, an hour away.
There's no way we'll make it in time.
She's got her cell. You could call her.
I am not doing this over the phone.
You don't have any other choice.
Hello?
Rachel. Oh, good.
By the way, did you just get on the plane?
Yeah.
We would have caught her...
-...if we were at the right airport.
Yay.
Um, Rachel, hang on.
No. No. No.
Phoebe, is everything okay?
Um...
Actually, no. No. You have to get off the plane.
What? Why?
I have this feeling that...
...something's wrong with it. Something is wrong with the left phalange.
Oh, honey, I'm sure there's nothing wrong with the plane.
Look, I have to go. I love you, and I will call you the minute I get to Paris.
Um, ahem...
What was that?
Oh, that was just my crazy friend.
She told me to get off the plane because she had a "feeling" that there...
...was something wrong with the left phalange.
Okay. Uh, that doesn't sound good.
Oh, I wouldn't worry about it.
She comes up with this stuff, and she's almost never right.
But she is sometimes.
Well...
What are you doing?
I can't take this plane now.
Excuse me, sir. Where are you going?
I have to get off this plane.
Her friend has a feeling something's wrong with the left phalange.
Could I get some peanuts?
What's wrong with the plane?
There's nothing wrong.
The left phalange.
There's no "phalange."
Oh, my God. This plane doesn't even have a phalange.
I'm not flying on it.
Please sit down.
What's going on'?
We're getting off. There is no phalange!
This is ridiculous. I...
Yeah, okay.
All right. My job here is done.
That was impressive.
Yeah. You didn't even use the tools for most of it.
Yeah, they were just slowing me down.
All right. I gotta get back to the babies. See you girls later.
Sorry about the table, man.
Yeah.
You gonna buy a new one?
Probably not. No.
I don't know how much I'm gonna want to play after you go.
Well, at least we got these little guys out.
Yeah.
Aw, we were worried about you.
Hm.
I guess I better get used to things crapping in my hand, huh?
I'm gonna miss these little guys.
It was nice having birds around again.
Hey, you know what? Maybe we should keep them here with you.
What?
Yeah. We got a lot going on right now.
And plus, here, they'd have their own room.
I could get a goose!
You know, I think you're set with the poultry.
Thanks, man. You hear that, you guys?
You're gonna get to stay here. And it's good...
...you know, because, uh...
Because now you have a reason to come visit.
I think there may be another reason.
So, uh...
Awkward hug or lame cool-guy handshake?
Yeah, well, you know, lame cool-guy handshake.
Ma'am, I assure you, the plane is fine.
And you fixed the phalange?
Yes. The phalange's fixed.
In fact, we've put a whole lot of extra phalanges on board, just in case.
Paging Mr. Anderson. Mr. Josh Anderson.
Where is she?
I don't see her.
Rachel! Rachel Green!
There she is!
Rachel! Rachel!
Whoa, do you have a boarding pass?
No. I just have to talk to someone.
I'm sorry. You need a boarding pass.
No, no. But you don't...
Rachel!
What? Oh, my God. What are you guys doing here?
Okay. You're on.
What? What, Ross? Okay, you're scaring me. What's going on?
Okay. Thing is...
Yeah.
Don't go.
What?
Please, please stay with me. I am so in love with you. Please don't go.
Oh, my God.
I know. I know.
I shouldn't have waited till now to say it, but, um... That was stupid, okay? I'm sorry.
But I'm telling you now. I love you.
Do not get on this plane.
Miss, are you boarding the plane?
Hey, hey
I know you love me. I know you do.
Miss
I...
I... I have to get on the plane.
No, you don't.
Yes, I do.
I do. They're waiting for me, Ross.
I can't do this right now, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Rachel.
I'm so sorry.
I really thought she'd stay.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Well, that's it.
Everything's packed.
Wow.
This is weird.
I know.
Yeah.
Uh, does this mean there's nothing to eat?
I put three lasagnas in your freezer.
I love you.
Hey.
Hey. Did you guys make it in time?
Yeah, yeah. He talked to her, but, um, she got on the plane anyway.
Where's Ross?
He went home. He didn't want to see anybody.
Ross. Hi, it's me.
I just got back on the plane, and I just feel awful.
That is so not how I wanted things to end with us.
It's just that I wasn't expecting to see you.
And all of a sudden you're there and saying these things.
Now I'm just sitting here and thinking...
...of all the stuff I should have said and I didn't.
I mean, I didn't even get to tell you that I love you too.
Because of course I do. I love you.
I love you.
What am I doing? I love you.
I've got to see you. I've got to get off this plane.
Oh, my God.
Okay, excuse me.
Miss, please sit down.
No, I'm sorry. I'm really sorry, but I need to get off the plane.
I need to tell someone that I love them.
I can't let you off.
Let her off the plane!
You have to take your seat.
Oh, please, miss. You don't understand.
Try to understand!
Come on, miss, isn't there any way that you can just let me off the...?
No! No!
Oh, my God. Did she get off the plane? Did she get off the plane?
I got off the plane.
You got off the plane.
I do love you.
I love you too, and I am never letting you go again.
Okay. Because this is where I want to be. Okay? No more messing around.
I don't want to mess this up again.
Me neither. We're done being stupid.
Okay. It's you and me, all right? This is it.
This is it. Unless we're on a break.
Don't make jokes now.
Okay, please be careful with that. It was my grandmother's. Be careful.
Thank you.
If that falls off the truck, it wouldn't be the worst thing.
Wow.
I know.
Seems smaller somehow.
Has it always been purple?
Look around, you guys. This was your first home.
And it was a happy place, filled with love and laughter.
But more important, because of rent control, it was a frigging steal.
Hey, do you realize that, at one time or another, we all lived in this apartment?
Oh, yeah. That's true.
Uh, I haven't.
What about that summer during college that you lived with Grandma...
...and you tried to make it as a dancer?
Do you realize we almost made it 10 years without that coming up?
Oh, honey, I forgot. I promised Treeger that we'd leave our keys.
Oh, okay.
So I guess this is it.
Yeah.
I guess so.
This is harder than I thought it would be.
Oh, it's gonna be okay.
Come on.
Do you guys have to go to the new house now, or do you have some time?
We got some time.
Okay. Should we get some coffee?
Sure.
Where?